[
  {
    "question": "Who scored the first goal in the match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Pedro",
      "B. Abdoulaye Doucoure",
      "C. Roberto Pereyra",
      "D. Michy Batshuayi"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      3
    ],
    "current_event_index": 3,
    "index": 0,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team scored more goals in the first half?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Chelsea",
      "B. Watford",
      "C. Both teams scored equally",
      "D. No goals were scored"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      3,
      9
    ],
    "current_event_index": 9,
    "index": 1,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many goals had Michy Batshuayi scored by the end of the match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 1",
      "B. 2",
      "C. 3",
      "D. 4"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      22,
      30
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 2,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team had the most goals in the match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Chelsea",
      "B. Watford",
      "C. Both teams scored equally",
      "D. No goals were scored"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      3,
      9,
      11,
      22,
      27,
      30
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 3,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the last player to score in the match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Pedro",
      "B. Cesar Azpilicueta",
      "C. Michy Batshuayi",
      "D. Roberto Pereyra"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      30
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 4,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will there be more goals after the 25:40 mark in the second half?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Yes",
      "B. No"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      27,
      30
    ],
    "current_event_index": 22,
    "index": 5,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player is most likely to score next after the 25:40 mark in the second half?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Michy Batshuayi",
      "B. Cesar Azpilicueta",
      "C. Pedro",
      "D. Roberto Pereyra"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      27
    ],
    "current_event_index": 22,
    "index": 6,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team is more likely to score next after the 25:40 mark in the second half?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Chelsea",
      "B. Watford"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      27,
      30
    ],
    "current_event_index": 22,
    "index": 7,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many yellow cards have occurred so far?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 1",
      "B. 2",
      "C. 3",
      "D. 4"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      4
    ],
    "current_event_index": 4,
    "index": 0,
    "event_type": "yellow card"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team has received more yellow cards up to now?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Watford",
      "B. Chelsea",
      "C. Both teams have the same",
      "D. Neither team"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      4,
      5
    ],
    "current_event_index": 5,
    "index": 1,
    "event_type": "yellow card"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player received the last card?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Jose Holebas",
      "B. Adrian Mariappa",
      "C. Antonio Rudiger",
      "D. Alvaro Morata"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      4,
      5
    ],
    "current_event_index": 5,
    "index": 2,
    "event_type": "yellow card"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many total yellow cards occurred in the match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 3",
      "B. 4",
      "C. 5",
      "D. 6"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      4,
      5,
      6,
      13,
      24
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 3,
    "event_type": "yellow card"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team had the most yellow cards in the match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Watford",
      "B. Chelsea",
      "C. Both teams had the same",
      "D. Neither team"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      4,
      5,
      6,
      13,
      24
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 4,
    "event_type": "yellow card"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player was involved in the most yellow cards?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Jose Holebas",
      "B. Adrian Mariappa",
      "C. Antonio Rudiger",
      "D. Kiko"
    ],
    "answer": "D",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      4,
      5,
      6,
      13,
      24
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 5,
    "event_type": "yellow card"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will there be more yellow cards in this match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Yes",
      "B. No"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      6,
      13,
      24
    ],
    "current_event_index": 5,
    "index": 6,
    "event_type": "yellow card"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team is more likely to get the next yellow card?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Watford",
      "B. Chelsea",
      "C. Both teams",
      "D. Neither team"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      6
    ],
    "current_event_index": 5,
    "index": 7,
    "event_type": "yellow card"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player is most likely to be involved in the next yellow card?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Jose Holebas",
      "B. Adrian Mariappa",
      "C. Antonio Rudiger",
      "D. Alvaro Morata"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      6
    ],
    "current_event_index": 5,
    "index": 8,
    "event_type": "yellow card"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many corners have occurred so far?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 1",
      "B. 2",
      "C. 3",
      "D. 4"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1
    ],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 0,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team has taken more corners up to now?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Chelsea",
      "B. Watford",
      "C. Both teams have taken the same number",
      "D. Neither team has taken a corner"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1
    ],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 1,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who took the last corner kick?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Thibaut Courtois",
      "B. Cesc Fabregas",
      "C. Jose Holebas",
      "D. Roberto Pereyra"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1
    ],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 2,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many total corners occurred in the match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 5",
      "B. 10",
      "C. 12",
      "D. 15"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1,
      2,
      7,
      8,
      10,
      12,
      15,
      16,
      18,
      19,
      20,
      23,
      28
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 3,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team had the most corners in the match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Chelsea",
      "B. Watford",
      "C. Both teams had the same number",
      "D. Neither team had any corners"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1,
      2,
      7,
      8,
      10,
      12,
      15,
      16,
      18,
      19,
      20,
      23,
      28
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 4,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player was involved in the most corners?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Cesc Fabregas",
      "B. Jose Holebas",
      "C. Roberto Pereyra",
      "D. Andre Carrillo"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1,
      2,
      7,
      8,
      10,
      12,
      15,
      16,
      18,
      19,
      20,
      23,
      28
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 5,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will there be more corners in this match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Yes",
      "B. No",
      "C. Only one more",
      "D. It's impossible to predict"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      2,
      7,
      8,
      10,
      12,
      15,
      16,
      18,
      19,
      20,
      23,
      28
    ],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 6,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team is more likely to get the next corner?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Chelsea",
      "B. Watford",
      "C. Both teams are equally likely",
      "D. Neither team will get another corner"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      2,
      7,
      8,
      10
    ],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 7,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player is most likely to be involved in the next corner?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Cesc Fabregas",
      "B. Jose Holebas",
      "C. Roberto Pereyra",
      "D. Andre Carrillo"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      2,
      7,
      8,
      10
    ],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 8,
    "event_type": "corner"
  }
]